Herold J. Wiens Collection
Geography & Map Division Library of Congress
- [Nan-cheng, Shensi (Shaanxi), China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, 1944., 44; 1 Aerial Photograph 35 x 28 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Nan-cheng, Shensi
- [Fukien hills near Ho-tung,Xinjiang, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, 1944., 45; 1 Aerial Photograph 35 x 28 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given.; .; Access Points: China. Ho-tung, Xinjiang
- [Fujian, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, 1944., 46; 1 Aerial Photograph 35 x 28 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph with description a on the back.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Pai-shih, Fujian,Ho-tung River
- [Yunnan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, 1944., 47; 1 Aerial Photograph 35 x 28 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph with description a on the back.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Pao-shan, Yunnan
- [China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 48; 17 Aerial Photographs Various.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China.
- [Maps covering cities and walls,counties of different provinces in China], 49; 29 Aerial Photographs 18 x 12 cm.; Various; Format: Map; Photographs only.; Access Points: China.
- [China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 50; 1 Aerial Photograph 26 x 26 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Access Points: China. Sea-Land-Piers
- Fukien (Fujian), China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 51; 1 Aerial Photograph 25 x 23 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph with a description; "Sortie 4M9-24R"; Access Points: China. Shanghang Area, Fukien
- [Foochow (Fuzhou), Fujian, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 52; 1 Aerial Photograph 19 x 18 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph with a description; "Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Fuzhou, Fujian
- [Northwest Kwangsi and Chuang Autonomous Region, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 53; 2 Aerial Photographs 25 x 23 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions; "Sortie 4M9-137,138." Height Unknown.; Access Points: China. Ling-yuan, Kwangsi
- [Shensi (Shaanxi), China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 54; 1 Aerial Photograph 22 x 14 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph with a description; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Shensi
- [Szechwan (Sichuan), China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 55; 2 Aerial Photographs 21 x 21 cm; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Szechwan
- [Yunnan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 56; 4 Aerial Photographs 25 x 25 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Yunnan
- [Yunnan, China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 57; 2 Aerial Photographs 25 x 25 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: China. Kun-ming,Yunnan
- [Kweichow (Guizhou), China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 58; 5 Aerial Photographs 25 x 25 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions; "Sortie 4M9".; Access Points: China. Kweichow
- [China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 59; 9 Aerial Photographs 25 x 25 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only; Sortie identification number not given; Access Points: China.
- [China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, August 5, 1943., 60; Photo Index 56 x 50 cm.; 1:15,000; Format: Aerial Index only; Index only.; "Sortie 21PS M-8/28. Height 31,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China.
- [China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 5, 1942., 61; Photo Index 56 x 50 cm.; 1:12,500; Format: Aerial Index only; Index only.; "Sortie 3-9FS/76. Height 25,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China.
- [China] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, September 25, 1943., 62; Photo Index 56 x 50 cm.; 1:14,500; Format: Aerial Index only; Index only.; "Sortie 21PS/M9-3-B. Height 28,000 ft."; "North 23o East 113o "; Access Points: China.
- [Ailinginae Island, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 63; 8 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "North 11o 8' East 166o 24' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands Ailinginae Island, Kwajalein Islands
- [Maloelab Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 4, 1951., 64; 1 Aerial Photograph 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; "Sortie MI 24." Height Unknown.; "North 8o 45' East 171o 3' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands Maloelap Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Namorik Islet, Namorik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, February 29, 1952., 65; 7 Aerial Photographs 15 x 15 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 45." Height Unknown.; "North 5o 36' East 168o 7' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Namorik Atoll
- [Likiep Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, February 28, 1952., 66; 2 Aerial Photographs 15 x 15 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 45." Height Unknown.; "North 9o 53' East 169o 9' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands Likiep Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Gardner Atoll, Phoenix Islands, Kiribati] by United States. Air Force., 67; 1 Aerial Photograph 17 x 12 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "South 4o 40' West 174o 32' "; Access Points: Kiribati. Nikumaroro Islands
- [Ailuk Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 3 1951., 68; 6 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 32-24."; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Ailuk Atoll
- [Utirik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 3 1951., 69; 5 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 32-24."; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Utirik Atoll
- [Likiep Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 3 1951., 70; 12 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 32-24." Height Unknown.; .; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Likiep Atoll
- [Hull Island, Phoenix Islands, Kiribati] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, 1939., 71; 4 Aerial Photographs 25 x 21 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "South 4o 30' West 172o 5' "; Access Points: Kiribati. Hull Island, Phoenix Islands
- [Enderbury Island, Phoenix Islands, Kiribati] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, 1939,1950's., 72; 8 Aerial Photographs 25 x 21 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; "South 3o 3' West 171o 3' "; Access Points: Kiribati. Hull Island, Phoenix Islands
- [Gardner Island, Phoenix Islands, Kiribati] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, 1939., 73; 5 Aerial Photographs 25 x 21 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; Sortie identification number not given.; "South 3o 38' West 171o 35' "; Access Points: Kiribati. Gardner Island, Phoenix Islands
- [Kili, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, February 29, 1952., 74; 5 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 47." Height Unknown.; "North 5o 39' East 169o 4' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Kili, Kwajalein Islands
- [Wotje Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, March 3, 1952., 75; 29 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie MI 47." Height Unknown.; "North 9o 27' East 170o 2' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Wotje Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Rongerik, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 76; 4 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie MI 64." Height Unknown.; "North 11o 21' East 167o 26' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Rongerik Atoll,Kwajalein Islands
- [Arno Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 77; 9 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 59." Height Unknown.; "North 7o 5' East 171o 41' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Arno Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Majuro Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 78; 13 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 62." Height Unknown.; "North 7o 9' East 171o 12' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Majuro Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Ailuk Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 3,1951., 79; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs with some descriptions.; "Sortie 61." Height Unknown.; "North 10o 20' East 169o 56' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Ailuk Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Ujelang Islet, Ujelang Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, March 6, 1952., 80; 11 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 48." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Ujelang Atoll
- [Calalin Islet, Majuro Atoll, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, March 11, 1952., 81; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 50." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Majuro Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Utirik & Pigawak Islets, Utirik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, February 2, 1952., 82; 5 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 45." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Utirik & Pigawak Islets, Utirik Atoll
- [Ebon Islet, Ebon Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 9, 1951., 83; 13 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 7." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Ebon Islets, Ebon Atoll
- [Kejien & Lukunor Islet, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 84; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 13."Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Kejien Islet, Likiep Atoll
- [Matamat Islet, Namorik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, September 23, 1951., 85; 2 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 9." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Matamat Islet, Namorik Atoll
- [Ujelang Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 8, 1951., 86; 14 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 8." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Ujelang Atoll
- [Namu Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, September 29, 1951., 87; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 20." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Namu Island
- [Pikareji(Bikaridj) Islet, Arno Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 3, 1951., 88; 2 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 26 ". Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Arno Atoll
- [Enalik, Mili, Rigeeshi Islets, Mili Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 2 1951., 89; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 27." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Mili Atoll
- [Meijit(Mejit) Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 6, 1951., 90; 15 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 36." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Mejit Island
- [Wotja Islet, Ailinglapalap Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 7, 1951., 91; 2 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 36." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Ailinglaplap Atoll
- [Various Islets & Namu Atolll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 7, 1951., 92; 13 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 36." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Namu Atoll
- [Jaluit Island,Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 7, 1951., 93; 6 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 37." Heigth Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Jaluit Lagoon
- [Rongelap Atoll(Bigini), Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 27, 1951., 94; 13 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 40." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Rongelap
- [Mili, Arno, Ratak Atolls, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, February 2, 1952., 95; 2 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 43." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Ratak Atolls
- [Kili, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 96; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 47." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Kili Atoll
- [Jemo Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, August 18, 1952., 97; 6 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 65." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Jemo Island
- [Majuro Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 98; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 23." Height Unknown.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Majuro Atoll, Kwajalein Islands
- [Rongerik Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 99; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Rongerik Island
- [Rongerik Atoll, Rongerik Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 100; 1 Aerial Photograph 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Rongerik Island
- [Taongi Atoll,Taongi Island, Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 101; 16 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given.; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Taongi Island
- [Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, October 5, 1951., 102; 5 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 1." Height Unknown.; .; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Kwajalein Islands
- [Kwajalein Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, August 22, 1951., 103; 4 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 31." Height Unknown.; .; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Kwajalein Islands
- [Rongerik Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 4, 1951., 104; 5 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 33." Height Unknown.; .; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Rongerik Atoll
- [Island not Identified] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, March 4, 1952., 105; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 46." Height Unknown.; .; Access Points: Island not Identified.
- [Island not Identified] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, February 28, 1952., 106; 4 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 44." Height Unknown.; .; Access Points: Island not Identified.
- [Ujelang Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 6, 1951., 107; 4 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 38." Height Unknown.; .; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Ujelang Atoll
- [Island not Identified] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 21 1951., 108; 2 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; "Sortie MI 39." Height Unknown.; .; Access Points: Island not Identified.
- [Wotje Island, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 109; 3 Aerial Photographs 19 x 17.5 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given; "North 9o 27' East 170o 14' "; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Wotje Islands
- [Eniwetok Atoll, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 110; 1 Aerial Photograph 8 x10 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given; Access Points: Marshall Islands. Eniwetok Atoll
- [Puluwat Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, November 14, 1951., 111; 1 Aerial Photograph 8 x10 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given; Access Points: Caroline Islands. Puluwat Islands
- [Woleai Islands, Marshall Islands] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force, December 15, 1951., 112; 1 Aerial Photograph 8 x 10 cm.; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photograph only.; Sortie identification number not given; .; Access Points: Caroline Islands. Woleai Isalnds
- [Areas not Identified] by United States. Air Force. United States. Air Force., 113; 4 Aerial Photographs Various; Format: Aerial Photographs; Photographs only.; Sortie identification number not given; Access Points: Island not identified
- Manchuria 1920's[?]., 114; 1 Map 55 x 59 cm.; 1:6,300,000; Format: Map; Access Points: Manchuria Korea, Japan
- Manchuria 1920's[?]., 115; 1 Map 41 x 32 cm.; 1:6,300,000; Format: Map; Access Points: Manchuria
- Yawata & Kagoshima, Japan by United States. Army Map Services. United States. Army, 1945., 116; 1 Map 1460 x 1380 cm.; 1:250,000; Format: Map; Multiple maps attached.; Under direction of Chief of Engineers, AMGD; Access Points: Japan
- Korea by United States. Army Map Services. United States. Army, 1950's[?]., 117; 1 Map 1010 x 760 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. L302; Series sheets: Sheet 4. 4th Edition; Under direction of Chief of Engineers, AMGD; Access Points: Korea
- Southern Japan by United States. Army Map Services. United States. Army, 1946., 118; 1 Map 770 x 800 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Mercator; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. L302; Series sheets: Sheet 3. 4th Edition; Under direction of Chief of Engineers, AMGD; Access Points: Japan
- Japan by United States. Army Map Services. United States. Army, 1945., 119; 1 Map 1260 x 1060 cm.; 1:2,000,000; Azimuthal Equidistant; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5204; Series sheets: 1st Edition; Access Points: Japan
- Yellow Sea Northern Portion by O.N.I. & M.I.D. War Department. United States. War Department, 1941., 120; 1 Map 770 x 1120 cm.; 1:500,000; Format: Map; No. 30 Yellow Sea Northern Portion.; Japanese Naval Air Chart. Chief of Engineers: U.S.A.; Access Points: Japan
- Nagoya by United States. Army Map Services. United States. Army, 1946., 121; 1 Map in 2 parts 1080 x 910 cm.; 1:250,000; Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5303; Series sheets: Sheet 19 and 20. 1st Edition; Japan Road Map. Under direction of Chief of Engineers,GDAM; Access Points: Japan
- Asia 1:1,500,000. Ch'eng-tu by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1943., 122; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,500,000; Gauss Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5304; Series sheets: Sheet X-12, "Ch'eng-tu", 2nd Edition-AMS 2; Copied from a USSR map dated 1940.; Access Points: China
- Asia 1:1,500,000. Hankow by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1943., 123; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,500,000; Gauss Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5304; Series sheets: Sheet X-13, " Hankow", 2nd Edition-AMS 2; Copied from a USSR map dated 1940.; Access Points: China
- Asia 1:1,500,000. Peip'ing by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1943., 124; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,500,000; Gauss Conformal Conic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5304; Series sheets: Sheet IX-13, "Peip'ing", 2nd Edition-AMS 2; Copied from a USSR map dated 1941.; Access Points: China
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Chungking by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1945., 125; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet N H-48, "Chunking", 1st Edition-AMS 3; Copied from Survey of India dated 1942.; Access Points: China
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Canton by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1945., 126; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,000,000; Modified Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet NF 49, "Canton", 1st Edition-AMS 3; Copied from China Proper dated 1945.; Access Points: China
- Eastern Asia 1:1,000,000. Changsha by United States. Army Map Services. Washington, D.C.: United States. Army, 1945., 127; 1 Map 660 x 710 cm.; 1:1,000,000; International Polyconic; Format: Map; Map series: A.M.S. 5301; Series sheets: Sheet N.H-49, "Changsha", 1st Edition-AMS 4; Copied from Survey of India dated 1944.; Access Points: China